trackapartner.com 2012-09-19

# Trackapartner.com | Track Your Partner | Free Cell Phone Tracker Service | Real Time Mobile Phone Locator

We at Trackapartner.com respect the privacy of our visitors and are committed to preserving your online safety by preserving your privacy at anytime you visit or communicate with our site.

Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy offers you a thorough explanation regarding your personal data provided to us or any data we may collect from you.

This Privacy Policy is updated from time to time; therefore, it should be reviewed occasionally.

**1\. Collected Information**  
Data can be collected and processed during the operations of our website. The following are ways we may perform these actions:

1.1 | Data regarding your visit(s) to our website and any resources used are collected. The following is included and not limited to: location data, weblogs, traffic data, and any other communication information.  
---|---  
1.2 | Any phone numbers entered in the "locate a phone" field, real or fake, will not, under any circumstances, be collected or stored in any way.  
  
**2\. Cookie Usage**  
Any information collected will not have any identifying data. It is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our site. No personal details will be shared that could identify you.

Our advertisers may download cookies to which we have no control. If used, these cookies are downloaded by clicking on an advertisement found on our website. 

**3\. Our Use of Your Information**  
Information stored or collected regarding you helps us improve and offer services you need. The following list contains how we might use your data:

3.1 | Any request you make of our site or personnel allows us to use information you provided us with, relating to the products or services we have.  
---|---  
3.2 | Contract Commitments: To meet any Commitment we make to you.  
3.3 | Changes or Improvements made to the site can warrant use of your information, with regard to notification of such changes.  
3.4 |  Any new customer can only be contacted by us or third parties if consent has been offered via our site. We only send communications you have consented to.  
3.5 | None of the information collected about you will offer identifiable characteristics. Information shared to a third party is statistical only. We will not reveal who you are, only mathematical information about our visitors.  
  
**4\. Personal Data Storage**  
Information we are provided will be stored on secure servers. Transaction data is encrypted for your safety.

**5\. Information Disclosure**  
5.1 Third Party disclosure may occur for the following reasons:

5.2.1 | Selling any or all of our business to a third party may result in sharing your information.  
---|---  
5.2.2 | At any time when we are legally required to we may disclose information about you and your visits to our sites.  
5.2.3 | To prevent fraud and help in fraud protection in order to reduce credit risk, we may disclose information.  
  
**6\. Third Party Links**  
Third party links may be discovered on our site.  These third party links have their own privacy policy, which you agree to when you click on the link.  We are not responsible nor do we accept responsibility for third party links.  Our liability covers us only on our site, and thus we do not accept liability for third party links as we have no control over them. 

**7\. Information Accessibility**   
We cannot withhold data we collect about you, as per The Data Protection Act 1998. This act provides you with access to any information we may hold on you.  If you wish to have access about our data collection on you please pay our fee of €10.  The fee covers our costs for processing your request and getting the data to you.  Please use the contact details below to formulate your data access request.

**8\. Contacting Us**   
Please feel free to contact us with queries, requests, or comments you may have about our Privacy Policy.  We welcome any communication via the Contact us page.
